♪I'll go with you to see your favorite flower in spring♪
♪ سأذهب معك لرؤية زهرتك المفضلة في الربيع ♪ زهرتك المفضلة في الربيع ♪
♪I'll treat you to your favorite ice cream in summer♪
♪ سأدعوك لتناول الطعام إلى المثلجات المفضل لديك في الصيف ♪
♪I'll be with you in the rain when you're sad in autumn♪
♪ سأكون معك في المطر عندما تكونين حزينة في الخريف ♪
♪I'll build a snowman for you in winter♪
♪ سأبني ثلجا لك في الشتاء ♪
♪Only you can have my romance♪
♪ فقط يمكنك الحصول على رومانسي ♪
♪Everyone else is secondary♪
♪ كل شخص آخر في الثانوية ♪
♪I like your every smile and frown♪
♪ يعجبني كل ابتسامتك وفزع ♪
♪Please let me hold your hand♪
♪ من فضلك دعني أمسك يدك ♪
♪I want to take you to watch the stars♪
♪ أريد أن آخذك لمشاهدة النجوم ♪
♪Please♪
♪ يرجى ♪
♪Let me take care of you♪
♪ دعني أعتني بك ♪
♪Please let me hold your hand♪
♪ من فضلك دعني أمسك يدك ♪
♪When it's cold, hide in my arms♪
♪ عندما يكون بارد، يختبئ في ذراعيّ ♪
♪Drive all your sadness♪
♪ دفع كل حزنك ♪
♪Completely away♪
♪ على الفور ♪
=Falling In Love With Me= =Episode 20=
= المواءمة في الحب مع أنا = = الحلقة 20 =
(If I can't make it to the top three,)
(إذا لم أستطع الوصول إلى المراكز الثلاثة الأولى)
(I will be dropped by the company.)
(سوف تسقط من قبل الشركة)
(But if I use the necklace...)
(ولكن إذا استخدمت القلادة)
Are you ready?
هل أنت مستعد؟
Erbao,
إرباو
go for it!
هيا!
Save it.
أنقذه
I'd rather she didn't get an award and came back
أفضل أنها لم تحصل وعادت
to inherit our small convenience store.
لرث متجر البقالة الصغيرة لدينا
Dad, Mom,
أبي، أمي
thank you.
شكرًا لك
( I Am a Singer-songwriter) I've heard that there are
"أنا مغني - كاتب الأغنية" سمعت أن هناك
a couple of good candidates.
"أنا مغني - كاتب أغنية" عدة مرشحين جيدين
I have high hopes for them.
لدي آمال كبيرة لهم
Congratulations,
مبروك
Chief Director,
رئيس المدير
Shen Zhizhou.
شين تشتشو
Congratulations to you too.
مبروك لك أيضا
You finally found the person you love.
وجدت الشخص الذي تحبينه أخيرا
Let me ask you.
دعني أسألك
She's the reason why you're going to disclose
إنها السبب سبب الكشف
your identity this time?
هويتك هذه المرة؟
What if
ماذا لو
she doesn't win?
ألا تفوز؟
Okay, I get it.
حسنًا، فهمت
The person you like is definitely the best.
الشخص الذي تحبينه هو الأفضل بالتأكيد
Alright, I'll go ahead.
حسنًا سأذهب أنا
Okay.
حسنًا
Don't be nervous.
لا تتوتر
You've done very well.
أحسنت صنعًا
You can write good songs,
يمكنك كتابة أغاني جيدة
and your singing has improved a lot.
وتحسنت أغنيتك كثيرًا
Can I really do it?
هل يمكنني فعل ذلك حقًا؟
Of course.
بالطبع
You're the only apprentice of Lin Tongyu.
أنت المتدرب الوحيد من لين تونغيو
Go for it.
هيا
Tang Yutong.
تانغ يونغ
♪I like you so much♪
♪ أنا أحبك جدًا ♪
I've decided to listen to you.
قررت أن أستمع إليك
I won't use the superpower
لن أستخدم القوة الفائقة
of the necklace.
من القلادة
I trust myself.
أنا أثق بنفسي
Next up is the 58th contestant,
التالي هو المتسابقة 58
Tong Erbao.
تونغ إرباو
Please.
تفضل
- Erbao, come on.
- إرباو، هيا
Good luck.
حظًا موفقًا
- I support you - I support you.
- أنا أدعمك
(So it's Tong Yuxin who sings terribly.)
(لذلك فهو تونغ يو شين الذي يغلي بشكل رهيب)
(She has disappeared for several months.)
(لقد فقدت) لعدة أشهر
(Why is she called Tong Erbao?)
(لماذا تدعى تونغ إرباو)
(What an old-fashioned name.)
(يا له من اسم قديم)
(Right.)
(صحيح)
(I still use her horrible songs)
(ما زلت أستخدم أغانيها الفظيعة)
(as my alarm clock.)
(مثل ساعة الإنذار)
It's time for you all to feel
لقد حان الوقت لكم جميعا للشعور
the power of the president of Tong Erbao's fan club.
قوة الرئيس من نادي مُعجبي تونغ إرباو
(The 10th I Am a Singer-songwriter)
"العاشر أنا مغني - كاتب الأغنية"
(You're the only apprentice of Lin Tongyu.)
(أنت المتدرب الوحيد) من لين تونغ يو)
♪The sky is lonely but beautiful♪
♪ السماء واحدة لكنها جميلة ♪
♪I'm a speck of dust♪
♪ أنا غبار من الغبار ♪
♪Disguised as a star♪
♪ مبرز كنجم ♪
♪Wandering in the galaxy♪
♪ اجتذب في المجرة ♪
♪Without a purpose♪
♪ دون غرض ♪
♪In my heart♪
♪ في قلبي ♪
♪Lives romanticism♪
♪ أحيا الرومانسية ♪
♪I am careful♪
♪ أنا حذر ♪
How is it?
كيف الحال؟
♪Refusing to be confined to a certain place♪
♪ رفض أن يكون محصورا في مكان معين ♪
♪Freedom is beautiful♪
♪ الحرية جميلة ♪
♪Wandering in the boundless star-river♪
♪ تهزأ في نهر الجراد بلا حدود ♪
♪My heart doesn't belong to any place♪
♪ قلبي لا ينتمي إلى أي مكان ♪
♪I can't admit that I am tired♪
♪ لا يمكنني الاعتراف بأنني متعب ♪
♪I also want a bit of comfort♪
♪ أريد أيضا بعض الراحة ♪
♪Fortunately, I bumped into your trajectory♪
♪ لحسن الحظ، أصبت في المسار ♪ إلى مسارك ♪
♪The huge magnetic field grabs me tightly♪
♪ المجال المغناطيسي الضخم أمسكي بي بإحكام ♪
♪I want to spin with you♪
♪ أريد أن أتجسس معك ♪
♪Into the next century♪
♪ حتى القرن القادم ♪
♪However happy I am on my own♪
♪ ومع ذلك فأنا سعيد بنفسي ♪
♪It can't beat your gentle gravity♪
♪ لا يمكن التغلب على خطوتك الحمقاء ♪
♪Over time♪
♪ على مر الوقت ♪
♪I merge with you♪
♪ أنا أندمج معك ♪
She sang really well.
كانت غنية حقا
Yes, it's quite melodious.
نعم، إنه رديء جدًا
Good!
جيد!
Erbao!
إرباو!
Great job!
أحسنت!
She sang really well.
كانت بارعةً في الغناء حقًا
Yes.
نعم
The third-place winner of this singer-songwriter competition is
الفائز في المركز الثالث من هذه المسابقة بين المغني والكاتب هو
Tong Erbao.
تونغ إرباو
Let's give her applause.
دعنا نصفق لها
Yeah!
نعم!
Well done.
أحسنت
It's a comeback victory.
إنه انتصار مرة أخرى
Today,
اليوم
we are very honored to have
يشرفنا كثيرا أن يكون لدينا
a mysterious award presenter here.
مقدم جائزة غامضة هنا
Congratulations.
تهانينا
But
لكن
I only got the third place.
حصلت على المركز الثالث فقط
Silly.
سخيفة
I am proud of you.
أنا فخور بك
♪Your love for me♪
♪ حبك لي ♪
That's so nice.
هذا جميل جدًا
How happy they look.
كم يبدون سعيدين
What a perfect match.
يا لها من مباراة مثالية
Yes.
نعم
♪Until the equator's light embraces the Antarctica♪
♪ حتى ضوء الاستواء يشمل أنتاركتيكا ♪
♪Maybe I can embrace you too♪
♪ ربما يمكنني أن أعتز بك أيضا ♪
♪Even though that's the farthest Antarctica♪
♪ على الرغم من أن هذه أبعد أنتاركتيكا ♪
♪Until the equator's light melts Antarctica♪
♪ حتى ضوء الاستواء يذوب أنتاركتيكا ♪
♪Your love for me♪
♪ حبك لي ♪
♪Might just reveal a little clue♪
♪ كل ما في الأمر أنها تكشف عن دليل قليل ♪
♪So I can find you♪
♪ حتى أتمكن من العثور عليك ♪
(Here's a bonus clip.)
(إليك علاوة نجدة)
=Falling In Love With Me=
= ملابس مع أنا =
Lady,
سيدتي
we finally meet again.
التقينا أخيرًا مجددًا
I'll give this back to you.
سأعيد هذه لك
Are you really no longer in need of it?
هل لم تعد بحاجة إليها حقًا؟
Thank you.
شكرًا لك
I think
أعتقد
I've found something even more precious than the superpower.
لقد وجدت شيئا أكثر ثمنا من القوى العظمى
♪Neither love nor hate can describe our relationship now♪
♪ لا الحب ولا الكراهية يمكن وصف علاقتنا الآن ♪
♪Being friends will only make each other awkward♪
♪ العثور على أصدقاء فقط جعل بعضنا البعض محرجا ♪
♪In the few weeks after breaking up♪
♪ في الأسابيع القليلة بعد الانفصال ♪
♪I restrain myself from missing you♪
♪ أنا أكبح نفسي عن فقدك ♪
♪Like a chronic disease, it comes and goes♪
♪ مثل مرض مزمن يأتي ويذهب ♪
♪Maybe I'm to blame for loving too deeply♪
♪ ربما أنا يجب أن ألقي اللوم للحب بعمق ♪
♪Will time heal the heartbreak♪
♪ سيكون وقت شفاء قلبية ♪
♪Or will it make it more painful♪
♪ أو سيجعل الأمر أكثر إيلاما ♪
♪Missing you is an incurable disease♪
♪ مفقودة كمرض عضال ♪
♪Yet now I think of you again♪
♪ أفكر فيك الآن مرة أخرى ♪
♪Neither love nor hate can describe our relationship now♪
♪ لا الحب ولا الكراهية يمكن وصف علاقتنا الآن ♪
♪Being friends will only make each other awkward♪
♪ العثور على أصدقاء فقط جعل بعضنا البعض محرجا ♪
♪I am not afraid of lonely nights♪
♪ أنا لست خائفا من الليالي وحيدة ♪
♪Everyone knows it is a lie♪
♪ الجميع يعرفون أنها كذبة ♪
♪I don't want to bear the pain of missing again♪
♪ لا أريد أن أتحمل ألم المفقودين مرة أخرى ♪
♪Can you please let me go♪
♪ هل يمكنك أن تسمحي لي بالمغادرة ♪
♪The carriage of time won't stop♪
♪ مرور الوقت لن يتوقف ♪
♪I'm sorry. I can't be the person you're with for the rest of your life♪
♪ أنا آسف، لا يمكن أن أكون الشخص أنت مع بقية حياتك ♪